[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mortimer, one of the main characters in Arsenic and Old Lace is trying to commit  his brother Teddy into which mental institution?", "correct_answer": "Happydale Sanitarium", "incorrect_answers": ["Nuttyburgh Sanitarium", "Pinetree Sanitarium", "Sunnydays Sanitarium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dark chocolate reduces blood pressure while enhancing circulation.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is the raccoon native to Europe?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the end of this great movie Jack gives Jonathan something to remember their adventure together. What does he give Jonathan at the end of the movie?", "correct_answer": "his wrist watch", "incorrect_answers": ["a picture of himself", "his detective shield", "a pack of cigarettes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the female body the breasts are organs of the reproductive system.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "New York Alki was a settlement which became part of which US city?", "correct_answer": "Seattle", "incorrect_answers": ["Atlanta", "Orono", "Savannah"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1867, Alfred Nobel introduced the first Pyrotechnic Fuse blasting cap, using what primary explosive to detonate dynamite?", "correct_answer": "Mercury fulminate", "incorrect_answers": ["Lead azide", "Hydrogen peroxide", "Black powder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The national motto of this South American country is Libertad o muerte, Spanish for Liberty or Death.", "correct_answer": "Uruguay", "incorrect_answers": ["Peru", "Argentina", "Brazil"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was used to help people hear before the hearing aid was invented?", "correct_answer": "Ear Trumpet", "incorrect_answers": ["Ear Headpiece", "Ear Windtrophy", "Ear Microphone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of animal is Marley from the 2008 drama-comedy movie Marley  Me, starring Jennifer Aniston and Owen Wilson?", "correct_answer": "Dog", "incorrect_answers": ["Chinchilla", "Horse", "Monkey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What were the main characters on Weird Science wearing on their heads when the created Lisa?", "correct_answer": "Bras", "incorrect_answers": ["Ski caps", "Underwear", "Nothing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sinkholes, natural depressions in the surface topography, may vary largely in size.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]